mindfieldonline.com 2015-10-13

# MindField - What's on Your Mind?

### Privacy Policy

**Effective On 09/04/2014**

This privacy policy applies to [http://mindfieldonline.com]() owned and operated by McMillion Research. This privacy policy describes how McMillion Research collects and uses the personal information you provide on our web site: [http://mindfieldline.com](). It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

McMillion Research has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, [http://mindfieldonline.com]().

TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy Trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at:

**Email Address:**  

**Phone Number:**  
800.969.9235

**Fax Number:**  
304.343.6522

**Postal Address:**  
MindField Online c/o McMillion Research LLC  
1012 Kanawha Blvd. East, Suite 301  
Charleston, WV 25301

*** Please note in any correspondence that the inquiry is in regard to the** [Privacy Policy](http://mindfieldonline.com/page/privacy)

If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request)

## Information Collection and Use

**Registration**

To use this website, first complete the registration form and create a user name and password. During registration, you are required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest such as participating in our surveys.

You have the option to provide demographic information (such as income level, gender and zip code). We encourage you to submit this information since omission of this information may hinder your being eligible to participate in certain surveys.

McMillion Research is the sole owner of the information collected on MindField Online. McMillion Research collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our website.

**Surveys**

We provide you the opportunity to participate in multiple surveys on our site. We may use a third-party service provider to conduct these surveys; however, we will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice. For example, if you agree to participate in a product test, we may need to share your personal information such as your name and mailing address with our client in order for the client to send you the product that you will be testing. In these cases you will be notified prior to our sharing the information and you can choose whether to in the product test. We would not allow our clients to use your information for any other purpose other than to send you the product to be tested. For reward purposes, a randomly generated unique identifier will be used for completion tracking.

**Facebook**

Information obtained via Facebook integration is the sole property of McMillion Research as long as the member chooses to associate the information. The member has complete control within the Facebook application of what information is shared and integration with MindField Online. This information is not required for MindField Online membership. All privacy statements, policies, and business related actions with information obtained via Facebook fall under the same distinctions as the remainder of this privacy policy, in full and in part. You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

**Referral System**

If you choose to use our referral service to tell friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. McMillion Research stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.

Your friend may contact us at [privacy@mindfieldonline.com](mailto:privacy@mindfieldonline.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

## Communications from the Site

**Invitations**

When you pre-qualify for a study you will be sent an invitation email from us. You may not opt-out of this email at this time without unsubscribing from [http://mindfieldonline.com]().

**Service-related Announcements**

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email.

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.

**Customer Service**

Based on the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email, telephone or text, in accordance with your wishes.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

**Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)**

As a data collection facility, we share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners and advertisers. This information does not identify individual users. In cases where we need to link aggregate user data associated with a specific individual for reward purposes and the like, we will associate a randomly generated unique identifier.

**Personally Identifiable Information**

We do not share, sell, or rent personally identifiable information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy without first providing you notice. Such information is needed for online focus groups and recruitments. If personal information is required, you will be notified before you participate. Your continued participation in the study after this notification acknowledges that you agree to the sharing of your personal information.

**Service Providers**

We utilize Integration Inc. to provide check writing services for our company. Upon your request for payment, we will provide Integration Inc. your name, address and payment amount to be processed. We do not utilize any other third party service providers other than what has been mentioned here.

Integration Inc. is strictly prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose.

**Legal Disclaimer**

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

## Opt-out

We provide you the opportunity to opt-out of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information.

If you no longer wish to participate in our surveys and receive survey invitations, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at [helpdesk@mindfieldonline.com](mailto:helpdesk@mindfieldonline.com).

## Log Files

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. 

## Cookies

We use cookies to remember users' settings and for authentication purposes. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited. Additionally, some cookies are used to help include you in specific client surveys. You can also reject these but it would keep you from receiving those special opportunities.

## Tracking Technology

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by McMillion Research and our marketing research partners, affiliates, and online customer support provider. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

## Social Media Widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button [and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

## Links to Other Sites

This website may contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by McMillion Research. Please be aware that we, McMillion Research, are not responsible for the privacy practices of other such sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.

This privacy policy applies only to information collected by this Website.

We may share your personal information and/or social-demographic information, including, without limitation, a unique identification number ("UID"), zipcode/postal code, date of birth, gender, marital status, education, ethnicity/race (where permitted by applicable law), employment related information, and non-personally identifiable information on household members, with third party sample/market research companies (individually each a "Third Party MR Company" and collectively the "Third Party MR Companies") for the purpose of identifying survey opportunities that you may be eligible for through the Third Party MR Companies. If you are eligible for a survey opportunity, the Third Party MR Company will provide your unique identification number and a survey link to us and we will invite you to participate in the survey. We will not share your name, email address, or phone number with the Third Party MR Companies. If you have any questions about this data sharing or want to opt-out of the data sharing please contact us at [helpdesk@mindfieldonline.com](mailto:helpdesk@mindfieldonline.com). Your participation in such survey opportunities does not entitle you to any benefits offered by or membership with the Third Party MR Companies.

## Co-branded sites

Co-branding is the method of having a user connect with a different website but make it appear to be the same site. In certain circumstance our clients may prefer to host the questionnaires themselves. If this is the case, the questionnaires may appear to be from [http://mindfieldonline.com](). Information provided to the clients is outlined in the Information Sharing and Disclosure section.

## Access to Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at [helpdesk@mindfieldonline.com](mailto:helpdesk@mindfieldonline.com) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements

## Security

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100 percent secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our website, you can emails at [privacy@mindfieldonline.com](mailto:privacy@mindfieldonline.com).

## Business Transitions

In the event McMillion Research goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email or prominent notice on our website for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

## Changes in This Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy policy, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page prior to the change becoming effective.

## Contact Us 

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us using one of the following options below:

**Email Address:**  

**Phone Number:**  
800.969.9235

**Fax Number:**  
304.343.6522

**Postal Address:**  
MindField Online c/o McMillion Research LLC  
1012 Kanawha Blvd. East, Suite 301  
Charleston, WV 25301
